Music
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
We'll start with the first question.
What is your name?
My name is Takato Okura. Please give me your best regards.
What is the origin of your name?
Takato means "person in the sky" in Japanese,
I think it means "to grow up big and tall like the sky.
What does your mother say about you?
My mother called me many different things,
Takato, Ta-chan, Taka, and so on.
My members, for example, Masaya Sakuragi calls me Takati, and I think there are four of them.
Where are you from?
I am from Kanagawa Prefecture.
What is your birthday?
My birthday is April 12, 2002.
What is your blood type?
My blood type is O.
What is your favorite part of your face?
My lips.
What are your hobbies?
Recently, I've been watching a lot of live videos of artists.
I've noticed that I've been watching a lot of live videos of artists that I'm really into at the moment.
I find myself watching a lot of live videos of artists I'm really into at the moment.
What are your special skills?
I say I'm good at swimming, but I didn't start swimming until the 6th grade.
But I only swam in the 6th grade of elementary school.
After that, I haven't been able to find anything that can be called a special skill.
So let's just say swimming for now.
Do something interesting?
Yes, I do.
Yeah.
I've been doing this for a long time, and he said, "Why are you doing that when you see this?
And when my brother got older, he said, "I can do that now.
What's your favorite food?
Recently, it's omu-rice.
I really like omu-rice with demi-glace sauce and not ketchup.
My least favorite food is
Vegetables.
What is your favorite color?
My favorite colors are black and gold.
Strengths
My strengths are...
I have a loud voice and a smooth tongue.
Disadvantages
Extremes.
Quirks.
I'm always right.
What is your charm point?
Well... my cheeks, I guess.
Yes, my cheeks.
What do you want to fix in your personality?
Extremes
What made you laugh the most recently?
The funniest thing that happened recently was...
When Koizumi Kouji remembered the names of his works in a completely different way.
It was very funny.
What are you worried about these days?
When I get absorbed in something, I lose track of time.
Sometimes it's 5 or 4 o'clock before I realize it.
I'm really concentrating on it.
It's a bit of a problem for me.
What is your daily routine?
I eat rice for breakfast.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
My best friend.
I'm not sure about this one.
I'm not sure about this one, but I'm thinking either the ability to stop time or instant travel.
If I had to choose between the two...
I'd have to say instantaneous movement.
If you won the lottery, what would you use it for?
First, I would give it to my parents.
I'd give it to my parents.
And then I would buy all the things I love right now.
How do you relieve stress?
Stress reliever?
Calling friends.
Lately, I've been going for a run at night because I'm pretty tired.
When I sleep, all my stress and worries are forgotten.
Stress and worries are forgotten the moment you fall asleep.
That's why I'm trying to make it that way.
I run to tire myself out and then go to bed.
You?
So, what now?
Well, that's a good question.
I think the best thing is...
I think it's people.
I think it's family and friends.
Members of the group.
What's your earliest memory?
I was playing hide-and-seek with my three kindergarten friends.
We were playing hide-and-seek in that classroom.
We were hiding under the desks.
And as we were hiding, out of the corner of my eye.
One of the girls had opened her locker.
And that's when our eyes met.
The moment you make eye contact with her.
Air guitar.
I'll take care of it.
There are many ways to play the guitar.
First of all, there's this one.
From the bottom.
And from the top.
Thumb.
I'm sorry, I'm not in the right tuning.
What's the gentlest thing you've played?
I think it's Kaname or Jun-kun.
I think Kaname or Jun-kun... but they're different.
Kaname is the one who tries to unify the opinions of those around him.
And Jun is the kind who follows up when things go wrong.
What's the toughest part of your act?
Ota is the strictest when it comes to dancing.
Kazuto is simply strict.
I also have a surprisingly strict side.
Please tell us about an unexpected aspect of each member.
Masaya looks like an adult, but he's a child.
Who has the most poker face in real life?
I guess Masaya.
He has a poker face, but his aura changes completely.
It's easy to tell.
But a poker face can replace a face, and a poker face can replace a face.
If I had to choose, I'd say Masaya.
What do you think you are in real life?
I don't know.
For better or worse, I'm like a catalyst.
One secret about yourself that the members don't know.
When I was in kindergarten, I used to braid one side of my hair at every event.
I used to braid one side of my hair.
I was a super funky kindergartener.
What's the one thing you can't lose?
It's a personality thing.
I have to win first place in everything.
I can't say I'm good at anything until I win first place.
Who would you like to meet?
Masaki Sugata.
What is your private room?
Talking on the phone with my best friend.
How do you spend your free time?
Basically on my off days
I sleep until I can sleep.
Call my friends to see if they are free and play games.
Go to my friend's house.
Or I do strength training.
What kind of kid were you?
I was in elementary school with my swimming buddies.
I'm a little different.
I think I was a child who changed from scene to scene.
Who is your favorite comedian?
Chidori.
If the earth were to die tomorrow, what would you do?
I would spend my?
I would spend all my money.
If you could be reborn, what would you want to be?
Shohei Otani.
If you could write one kanji character to describe yourself, what would it be?
Including the extremes I mentioned earlier.
Including what I said earlier about my personality.
I also said that I have to be No. 1.
Extreme of extreme.
I also mean extreme.
Where would you like to travel?
I really like the Witch of Takkebin.
The place where it's set
I heard that it was set in a place called Croatia.
Croatia.
I'd like to go there.
It's so big.
You forget bad things easily? Does it stick with you?
I think it drags on.
You have to talk to someone to get rid of it.
That's when you can use it.
Go for a run, get tired and go to bed.
What's your fetish?
That smell.
The detergent in my house smells so good.
I've had a fetish for it ever since.
And your mother?
I have a fetish for Korean cars.
What's your favorite outfit?
Wow!
That's nice.
I like the blue and the others, and the trilogy outfit.
What's your favorite onigiri ingredient?
Mentaiko (cod roe)
What is the most important thing to you?
Never betraying my best friend.
What is your favorite phrase in your part?
I like the song "Run Faster Than Pasogala.
I like the part where you and Jun-kun are talking to each other.
It's a phrase that says, "You know, you can break down your limits.
I was good at the gymnastics competition, like the three-legged race.
You know?
I think I practiced it so much with my friends that I was fast.
If you were to reward yourself, what would it be?
A week-long trip.
What is your favorite choreographed song?
Wow, there are so many!
The self-injurious "tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch tch.
The choreography!
I think it's a definite! I think I've got it.
What do you want to eat now?
Iekei Ramen
If you had 7 days off, what would you do?
I would like to go on a trip.
If you were a family of seven, what would your family consist of?
My mother
Jun-kun Papa
Kaname eldest son
Ji Nan Ryota
Sansan Kazuto
Grandpa Kousaku
Pet Masaya
Where would you like to sit in the classroom?
If you want to be cool
Window seat at the end of the hall
Where I actually chose when I switched seats
The very back of the middle row.
Composing Aigami in the Genji section
Aigami in the Genji section
There's no limit, you see!
Hmmm, what should I do?
Genji
eh?
Let's tear it up ourselves.
GENJI-BU!
To be frank, I can manage if I do that
Thanks to Pet Masaya
Thanks to Pet Masaya.
Nice! That's good.
What if I compare the members to oden?
Oh! Kosaku is like a konnyaku musubi.
Masaya, rice cake wrappers. Ryota, chikuwa, pure egg.
I think Kazuto is a daikon radish.
Kaname, let's split it in half.
Kaname's half.
Me?
I'll have...
Udon.
You know, the kind that you can make into a plus.
Oden.
Udon.
If you could change one aspect of yourself, what color would it be?
I wouldn't change it.
Well, finally
What do you think is the charm of the local section?
The attraction of the local club is...
When you actually go to a live concert, it's a lot of fun.
And it's a lot of fun!
I think this is the charm of the local club.
Which songs do you enjoy singing in the local group?
Dogs, Cats, Milk and Sugar.
Please describe your favorite emoji with your face.
I often use them on my blog.
What song do you recommend?
This one.
What did you have for breakfast today?
Fried chicken
What is the most relaxing or restful time of the day?
Sometimes the most restful time is running, isn't it?
When I'm absorbed in it, when I'm not really thinking about anything.
Running while listening to music is very restful.
What is essential for rehearsals?
Orange juice.
Orange juice is the drink that helps me recover when I'm tired, even if only a little.
I think orange juice is essential.
If you weren't acting or playing music, what would you be doing?
I was going to quit Wednesdays in the sixth grade and join the basketball team.
If I was really into it.
I probably would have been a basketball player.
What ideal has inspired you recently?
The moment when Craft was frustrated.
The fact that Kosaku is feeling frustrated.
I was quite inspired.
It made me want to work harder with him.
If you were an animal, what would you be?
A dog.
If a dog were an animal, what would it be?
If you could switch places for a day, who would you be?
It's hard to say.
One day.
Tenshin Nasukawa on fight day.
I'd like to be strong for a moment.
If you could perform outside of Japan, where would it be?
New York.
Because it's cool.
Who do you respect?
Masaki Sada.
And my father.
What movie have you seen recently or would you like to see?
A movie called "I fell in love like a bouquet of flowers.
Masaki Sugata is in it.
Because of my profession, and because of the story.
It's very touching.
What do you look for when choosing clothes?
Does it look good on me and do I want to wear it?
I try to buy clothes that I can't forget or that I wear instantly.
What kind of bread do you use at the bakery?
Mentaiko bread
What is your appeal point?
I update various social networking sites.
I keep myself updated on various social networking sites.
Please tell us three good things that happened this week.
The best thing that happened to me this week was
I played with my best friend at home.
I completed all the new Mario games!
I ate a delicious eel.
What keeps you going?
The comments on my blog.
Or the messages I get on the radio.
Or the one-word comments I get on insta-live, like how cute or cool they are.
Those are the things that really cheer me up.
What is your favorite side dish?
Macaroni salad.
What song would you say you and A are?
Bokura no Sekai Monogatari (Tale of Our World)
It's the highest pitch song I've ever sung.
And I simply love the lyrics.
What was your previous life?
Probably a farmer in the Okura family.
What would you like to do for the last comic act of your life?
Hmmm...
My mom made it.
Um...
Meat and eggs with ponzu sauce.
That's it.
Which seat do you like on the bullet train?
Basically, I don't have a preference.
But I think C seat because it's easy to go to the restroom.
Where do you want to go most now?
Tokyo Dome, I guess.
What foreign words have you learned recently?
Awww...
It's not really a word.
It's more like spelling.
I recently learned that the Spanish word
SPIN.
If you read it normally, it's "Spin".
Now I know it's Spanish!
Awww...
What is your motto?
My motto.
If you can't do it in the moment, don't think you can do it anywhere else.
Show us your favorite recent photo.
This one right here.
It's our first YouTube shoot.
Me, Kaname...
With Kousaku.
and Kousaku for our first YouTube shoot.
This is a picture of the three of us taken at that time.
First of all, I'd like to say
I've never done such a proper filming
I've never done it before.
We also had a barbecue together.
and talking about what we want to do in the future.
We talked a lot about what we want to do in the future.
I'll put the pictures here.
When do you feel happy in winter?
When I'm walking alone at night.
When your white breath goes fur...
What four-letter word makes you feel overwhelmed?
All my life.
What is your favorite sport?
Swimming
Basketball
What is the most impressive dream you had while sleeping?
Everything will be big except me.
Everything but me will be big.
What was your dream when you were a child?
To be a first-class architect.
And a long time ago...
Tomato shop.
Coffee? Tea?
Coffee.
What's your favorite Thomas?
Uh, like a double chocolate ring.
What's your favorite dish?
I served it to a craft once.
The craftsman said it was the best... a belly roll.
What would you like to try most right now?
Skydiving.
What Benjive song would you like people to listen to the most?
Lavender.
It's so simple, just ring the bell.
First of all, I love the lyrics of Lavender.
I love it so much.
As for the cymbals, it's a little difficult to play in the hall.
It's a little difficult to play in the hall.
I want people to remember this song.
What's your song of the year for Oates?
I'm going to change my socks
I'm going to change my socks to five-finger socks
One last thing...
Oh.
Oh, that's the last thing.
Uh...
Okranagazu.
Oh, so that's one word.
Can I say it again?
Recently.
Some of you have gotten to know us.
More and more.
You know, besides me.
You know, when I look at the questions...
I think everyone has a unique personality.
I think we all have unique personalities.
I hope you will continue to watch YouTube and the members' social networking sites.
I hope you will continue to visit us on YouTube and social networking sites of our members.
I hope you like Benjive more and more.
I hope you will like Benjib more and more.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Bye bye.